foreign
course this video will show you how the
platform works and the basics you need
to know to go effortlessly through your
courses
if at any time you want to skip this
video and get a first-hand experience of
the course all you have to do is click
on the next button that you will find
Above and Below on this page don't worry
I won't be offended
to begin let's look at the top of the
page
this area is called the navigation bar
here you will find the most essential
options for navigating your course
for example click on the course tab to
access the courses catalog and outline
clicking on the progress tab will reveal
how well you're doing in your studies
and exams when you take the demo course
we'll provide a simple progress report
matching your results
in the discussion tab you can
communicate with fellow students on
topics and projects and interact with
the course staff
you also may find other tabs containing
course announcements or any other
resources the course staff wanted to add
on the course catalog you will find the
entire course starting from the top down
typically a course is delivered in
sections like chapters divided into
subsections and units
for example the first section of this
course is the introduction and when you
click on it it displays the content of
the subsection
once you click on the subsection title
you can access the unit where each
class's content is
let's now look at the learning sequence
bar
each unit is represented in an item in
the bar above the content page revealing
a corresponding learning sequence
work your way from left to right
learning sequences can contain lectures
exercises and interactive lessons you
can complete on your schedule
its interactive lessons including
demonstrations visualizations and
virtual environments make the platform
fun and unique
the platform also supports more
traditional question format flight
multiple choice but also tests your
understanding by allowing you to use
simulators and even asking you to write
an essay interactive lessons are often
graded and contribute to your final
grade
you can see how the course's questions
for gauging your learning process can be
auto-graded or give detailed feedback in
real time
so while a course might be rigorous the
tools and visualizations are fun and
Interactive
finally students like to interact in
many ways to get the most out of a
course for example by participating in
discussion forums
engaging with others while taking a
course makes you more likely to succeed
now that you've seen how easy it is to
take a course here experience this
introduction course firsthand all you
have to do is go to chapter one by
clicking the next button